<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Baozhong DENG's Researches on Baozhong DENG's Page</title><link>https://MaximeMET.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Baozhong DENG's Researches on Baozhong DENG's Page</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://MaximeMET.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Niobium-carbide MXene Modified Hybrid Hole Transport Layer Enabling High-performance Organic Solar Cells Over 19%</title><link>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/006small/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/006small/</guid><description>Niobium-carbide (Nb2C) MXene as a new two-dimensional material has shown great potential for application in photovoltaics due to its excellent electrical conductivity, large surface area and superior transmittance. In this work, we have developed a novel solution-processable PEDOT:PSS-Nb2C hybrid hole transport layer (HTL) to enhance the device performance of organic solar cells (OSCs). By optimizing the doping ratio of Nb2C MXene in PEDOT:PSS, the best power convention efficiency (PCE) of 19.</description></item><item><title>High-throughput Computationally Guided Low/high Index Optical Coupling Layer for Record-performance Semitransparent Organic Solar Cells</title><link>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/005aem/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/005aem/</guid><description>Semitransparent organic solar cells (ST-OSCs) can be made in different colors, allowing light to pass through, and yet absorb enough visible and near-infrared (NIR) light to generate electricity. However, it remains a challenge to achieve high performing ST-OSCs over the two competing indexes of power conversion efficiency (PCE) and average visible transmittance (AVT). In this work, we report our effort to develop record-performance ST-OSCs using a low/high index optical coupling layer (OCL) and a 2-D photonic-structured antireflective (AR) coating.</description></item><item><title>Dual Photonic Structures Enable Semitransparent Organic Photovoltaics with Enhanced Light Utilization</title><link>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/004solrrl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/004solrrl/</guid><description>Semitransparent organic photovoltaics (ST-OPVs) offer promising prospects for self-powered greenhouses and building-integrated photovoltaic systems. However, it remains to be a critical challenge to balance the two competing indexes of power conversion efficiency (PCE) and average visible transmittance (AVT). Herein, we report our effort to develop high-performance ST-OPVs by employing dual photonic structures with a front single-layer optical coupling layer (OCL) and a rear single-layer antireflection coating (ARC). The material selection and thickness of both OCL and ARC have been systematically guided by combining theoretical simulation and experimental optimization, leading to significantly enhanced light utilization in ST-OPVs.</description></item><item><title>High-Performance Semitransparent Organic Solar Cells: From Competing Indexes of Transparency and Efficiency Perspectives</title><link>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/003advsci/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/003advsci/</guid><description>Semitransparent organic solar cells (ST-OSCs) offer potentially more opportunities in areas of self-powered greenhouses and building-integrated photovoltaic systems. In this work, the effort to use a combination of solution-processable gold nanobipyramids (AuNBPs)-based hole transporting layer and a low/high dielectric constant double layer optical coupling layer (OCL) for improving the performance of ST-OSCs over the two competing indexes of power conversion efficiency (PCE) and average visible transmittance (AVT) is reported. The fabrication and characterization of the ST-OSCs are guided, at design and analyses level, using the theoretical simulation and experimental optimization.</description></item><item><title>Plasmonics in Organic Solar Cells: Toward Versatile Applications</title><link>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/002acsaem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/002acsaem/</guid><description>Remarkable progress has been made in organic solar cells (OSCs), which are considered as one of the most promising next-generation photovoltaic technologies. Nevertheless, the inadequate light harvesting of the active layer with a limited thickness remains a critical challenge for high-performance OSCs. To address this issue, plasmonic nanostructures have been widely used to improve the light absorption and facilitate the charge extraction and collection in OSCs. In addition to the commonly reported approaches, this Spotlight focuses on the recent progress of three specific plasmonic applications in OSCs, namely, broadband optical enhancement from the visible to near-infrared wavelength region, semitransparent OSCs, and plasmonic electrodes, providing comprehensive insight into future plasmonic-enhanced OSCs toward versatile applications.</description></item><item><title>Ultraviolet-Durable Flexible Nonfullerene Organic Solar Cells Realized by a Hybrid Nanostructured Transparent Electrode</title><link>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/001solrrl/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://MaximeMET.github.io/post/001solrrl/</guid><description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://MaximeMET.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MaximeMET.github.io/about/</guid><description>Our lab of advanced photoelectric functional materials and devices. Currently, I am working in researches of semitransparent organic solar cells and nanostructures in organic photodetectors. My goal is to develop devices with record performances.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://MaximeMET.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MaximeMET.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Work in progress&amp;hellip;
Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message</description></item></channel></rss>